Every story ever written is just waiting to become real.
Inkheart is a adventure, family, fantasy film directed by Iain Softley.
The adventures of a father and his young daughter, in their search for a long
lost book that will help reunite a missing, close relative.
Mo 'Silvertongue' Folchart, played by Brendan Fraser.
Resa, played by Sienna Guillory.
Capricorn, played by Andy Serkis.
Meggie Folchart, played by Eliza Bennett.
Dustfinger, played by Paul Bettany.
Fenoglio, played by Jim Broadbent.
Inkheart is a 2008 fantasy adventure film directed by Iain Softley, produced by Cornelia Funke, Dylan Cuva, Sarah Wang, Ute Leonhardt, Toby Emmerich, Mark Ordesky, Ileen Maisel and Andrew
Licht, written by David Lindsay-Abaire, music composed by Javier Navarrete and starring Brendan Fraser, Paul Bettany, Helen Mirren, Jim Broadbent, Andy Serkis, and Eliza Bennett.
It is based on Cornelia Funke's 2003 novel of the same name.
Produced by New Line Cinema, the film was released theatrically on December 12,
2008, in the UK and January 23, 2009, in the US by Warner Bros.
Inkheart received mixed reviews from critics and
grossed $62,450,361 on a $60 million budget.
Inkheart was released on DVD and Blu-ray in the
United Kingdom on April 13, 2009.
On January 12, 2009, a video game based on the film
was released for the Nintendo DS.
The film explores themes of fairy tale, supernatural,
eavesdropping, writer's block, unicorn.